Hey, welcome back. In this section, we actually covered quite a lot of stuff.
嘿，欢迎回来。在这一节中，我们实际上涵盖了相当多的东西。
Now we have a working physics for our climbing, and you understand all the math operations that we need to pull this off.
现在，我们有了一个用于攀爬的物理学原理，你也明白了我们需要的所有数学运算来完成这个任务。
And our system is really coming together.
而我们的系统也正在形成。
Now that we have the climbing movement ready, it's time that we start to use some actual climbing animation and not this default walking animation.
现在我们已经准备好了攀爬动作，是时候开始使用一些实际的攀爬动画，而不是默认的行走动画。
And we'll look at how we can do that in the next section.
我们将在下一节看看我们如何做到这一点。
Before we move on, there's one more thing that I want to do. So I'm going to first close my project.
在我们继续之前，还有一件事我想做。所以我将首先关闭我的项目。
Instead of this custom movement component, I'm going to remove all the debug functions inside of it.
取而代之的是这个自定义运动组件，我将删除它里面的所有调试函数。
So I'm going to select this and press Ctrl+F to search.
所以我要选择这个，然后按Ctrl+F进行搜索。
So I'm going to first remove this line and remove this can start climbing.
所以我要首先删除这一行，并删除这个可以开始爬行。
Remove this else case.
删除这个别的情况。
And that's all for all of those debug functions.
这就是所有这些调试函数的全部内容。
And I'd also like to remove the debug shape for our capsule.
而且我还想删除我们的胶囊的调试形状。
So I'm going to scroll down to this trace climb both surfaces.
所以我将向下滚动到这个追踪爬升的两个表面。
And for this do capsule trace multi here, I'm going to remove this too.
对于这个做胶囊的跟踪多在这里，我也要去掉这个。
So now we won't be able to see the debug shape.
所以现在我们将无法看到调试形状。
All right, that's pretty much it. I'm going to compile here.
好了，差不多就是这样了。我将在这里进行编译。
I have a successful compile. And starting from next section, we'll look at how we can make this system much more interesting.
我有一个成功的编译。从下一节开始，我们将看看如何让这个系统变得更有趣。
When you're ready, I'll see you in the next section.
当你准备好了，我们在下一节见。